It was really hard
to book this cake
Thank you
I really wanted
my end the year
to be like this
Christmas with you
Hyesung
It's a huge success, huh?
But why didn't you
tell her earlier?
What?
Am I not your lover?
Ah, that's…
How did you save my name
in your phone?
Well…
Don't tell me
it's just "Shin Yoo-il"
Hey, it's Christmas
Why don't we
put some candles?
Let's put them here
and make a wish
I have no wish
I shouldn't wish more
than this
Come on, make a wish
What about you?
The wish is
supposed to be…
a secret
It's a Christmas gift
Oh no
I didn't prepare
anything
So
aren't you gonna tell me
what wish you made?
I just wished
my next year
to be as happy as now
with you